type Question = {
    question: string;
    answers: string[];
    correctAnswer: string;
  };


export const integumentarydata = {
 questions: [
    {
        question: "Human body is covered by skin that has three layers. Most superficial layer of the skin is?",
        answers: ["Dermis",
         "Epidermis",
        "Subcutaneous tissue",
        "Deep fascia",
        "Basement membrane"],
        correctAnswer: "Epidermis"
    },
    {
        question: "Which layer of skin is avascular?",
        answers: ["Dermis",
         "Epidermis",
        "Subcutaneous tissue",
        "Deep fascia",
        "Superficial fascia"],
        correctAnswer: "Epidermis"
    },    
    {
        question: "Thickness of epidermis is variable in different parts of body. Where is the epidermis extremely thick to withstand wear and tear?",
        answers: ["Back",
         "Face",
        "Palms and soles",
        "Thighs",
        "Abdomen"],
        correctAnswer: "Palms and soles"
    },
    {
        question: "Skin contains almost all types of tissues. What type of tissue composes the epidermis?",
        answers: ["Adipose tissue",
         "Loose connective tissue",
        "Epithelium",
        "Cartilage",
        "Bone tissue"],
        correctAnswer: "Epithelium"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of tissue composes the dermis?",
        answers: ["Adipose tissue",
         "Loose connective tissue",
         "Dense connective tissue",
         "Cartilage",
         "Bone tissue"],
         correctAnswer: "Loose connective tissue"
    },
    {
        question: "What connects the dermis to the underlying deep fascia or bones?",
        answers: ["Epidermis",
         "Subcutaneous tissue",
         "Hair follicles",
         "Stratum corneum",
         "Dermal papillae"],
         correctAnswer: "Subcutaneous tissue"
    },
    
    {
        question: "There ars appendages of the skin that include Nails, hair follicles, sebaceous glands, and",
        answers: ["Bones",
         "Cartilage",
         "Sweat glands",
         "Nerves",
         "Lymphatics"],
         correctAnswer: "Sweat glands"
    },
    {
        question: "What are nails composed of?",
        answers: ["Collagen",
         "Keratin",
         "Hyaline cartilage",
         "Elastin",
         "Fibroblasts"],
         correctAnswer: "Elastin"
    },
    {
        question: "The nails are keratinized plates on the dorsal surfaces of the tips of the fingers and toes. The proximal edge of the plate is",
        answers: ["root of the nail",
         "Nail plate",
         "Nail bed",
         "Nail fold",
         "Nail matrix"],
         correctAnswer: "root of the nail"
    
    },
      
    {
        question: "An oily material secreted by sebaceous glands is called",
        answers: ["Sweat",
        "Sebum",
         "Watery fluid",
         "Serous fluid",
         "Lymph"],
         correctAnswer: "Sebum"
    },    
    {
        question: "The superficial fascia, or subcutaneous tissue, is a mixture of loose areolar and adipose tissue. Where is superficial fascia devoid of adipose tissue?",
        answers: ["Scalp",
         "Back of the neck",
         "Palms of the hands",
         "Auricle of the ear",
         "Soles of the feet"],
         correctAnswer: "Auricle of the ear"
    },
    {
        question: "The deep fascia is a membranous layer of connective tissue. What does the deep fascia invest?",
        answers: ["Only the skin",
         "Only the bones",
         "Muscles",
         "Superficial fascia",
         "Nail bed"],
         correctAnswer: "Muscles"
    },
    {
        question: "The deep fascia is a membranous layer of connective tissue and it extends as septa in between muscles in",
        answers: ["Thorax",
         "Neck, ",
         "Abdomen",
         "Limbs",
         "Scalp"],
         correctAnswer: "Limbs"
    },
    {
        question: " In the region of joints, the deep fascia may be considerably thickened to form restraining bands called retinacula. What is the function of retinacula?",
        answers: ["Hold underlying tendons",
         "Support hair follicles",
         "Produce sebum",
         "Provide nutrients",
         "Transmit nerve signals"],
         correctAnswer: "Hold underlying tendons"
    },
    {
        question: "What helps explain the path taken by an infection during its spread?",
        answers: ["Superficial fascia",
         "Deep fascia",
         "Sebaceous glands",
         "Sweat glands",
         "Hair follicles"],
        correctAnswer: "Deep fascia"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of gland is responsible for producing sweat?",
        answers: ["Sebaceous gland",
         "Ceruminous gland",
         "Sweat gland",
         "Mammary gland",
         "Endocrine gland"],
         correctAnswer: "Sweat gland"
    },
    {
        question: "Hairs grow out of follicles, which are invaginations of the epidermis into the dermis. Hairs grow on?",
        answers: ["Eyelids",
         "Palms of the hands",
         "Soles of the feet",
         "Sides of fingers",
         "Sides of toes"],
         correctAnswer: "Eyelids"
    },
    {
        question: "The arrector pili connects the undersurface of the follicle to the superficial part of the dermis. What is the main function of sebaceous glands?",
        answers: ["Produce sweat",
         "Produce sebum",
         "Produce melanin",
         "Produce keratin",
         "Produce collagen"],
         correctAnswer: "Produce sebum"
    },  
    
        {
            question: "Which structure is responsible for dimpling of the skin surface, so-called gooseflesh?",
            answers: ["Sebaceous glands",
             "Sweat glands",
             "Arrector pili",
             "Hair follicles",
             "Epidermis"],
             correctAnswer: "Arrector pili"
        },
        
        {
            question: "Which condition is characterized by a yellow appearance of the skin due to liver disorder?",
            answers: ["Erythema",
             "Jaundice",
             "Cyanosis",
             "Melanoma",
             "Psoriasis"],
            correctAnswer: "Jaundice"
        },
        {
            question: "What causes the blue appearance of the skin known as cyanosis?",
            answers: ["Increased bilirubin",
             "Dilated blood vessels",
             "Deoxygenated hemoglobin",
             "Skin infection",
             "Hyperpigmentation"],
            correctAnswer: "Deoxygenated hemoglobin"
        },
        
        {
            question: "25 years man presented for lump in head and Surgeon reassured that it is due to sebum-producing-structure in the skin and may disappear. Which structure in the skin is responsible for producing sebum?",
            answers: ["Sweat glands",
             "Sebaceous glands",
             "Hair follicles",
             "Epidermis",
             "Subcutaneous tissue"],
            correctAnswer: "Sebaceous glands"
        },
        
        {
            question: "Which term refers to bands of thin wrinkled skin that appear during pregnancy?",
            answers: ["Keloids",
             "Dermatitis",
             "Erythema",
             "Striae gravidarum",
             "Cyanosis"],
            correctAnswer: "Striae gravidarum"
        },
        {
            question: "Which part of the skin contains collagen and elastic fibers that provide strength and flexibility?",
            answers: ["Epidermis",
             "Dermis",
             "Subcutaneous tissue",
             "Superficial fascia",
             "Hair follicles"],
            correctAnswer: "Dermis"
        },
        
        {
            question: "The primary function of the skin ligaments is to connect dermis to?",
            answers: ["Hair follicles",
             "Sebaceous glands",
             "Deep fascia",
             "Sweat glands",
             "Fat"],
            correctAnswer: "Deep fascia"
        },
        
        {
            question: "What are the primary cells found in the epidermis?",
            answers: ["Melanocytes",
             "Keratinocytes",
             "Fibroblasts",
             "Adipocytes",
             "Osteocytes"],
            correctAnswer: "Keratinocytes"
        },
        {
            question: "Which layer of the skin contains the blood vessels and nerves?",
            answers: ["Epidermis",
             "Dermis",
             "Subcutaneous tissue",
             "Superficial fascia",
             "Stratum corneum"],
            correctAnswer: "Dermis"
        },
        
        {
            question: "Which pigment is primarily responsible for skin color?",
            answers: ["Carotene",
             "Hemoglobin",
             "Melanin",
             "Collagen",
             "Elastin"],
            correctAnswer: "Melanin"
        },
        {
            question: "There are different types of cells in the skin. Main role of melanocytes is to produce?",
            answers: ["keratin",
             "collagen",
             "melanin",
             "sebum",
             "sweat"],
            correctAnswer: "melanin"
        },
        {
            "question": "Skin has three main layers- Epidermis, Dermis and Subcutaneous tissue. Which layer of skin contains the most collagen fibers?",
            "option1": "Epidermis",
            "option2": "Dermis",
            "option3": "Subcutaneous tissue",
            "option4": "Superficial fascia",
            "option5": "Stratum corneum",
            correctAnswer: 2
        },
        
        {
            "question": "Which condition is characterized by the skin appearing abnormally red due to engorged capillary beds?",
            "option1": "Erythema",
            "option2": "Cyanosis",
            "option3": "Jaundice",
            "option4": "Melanoma",
            "option5": "Psoriasis",
            correctAnswer: 1
        },
        
        {
            "question": "Which part of the skin contains sensory receptors for touch?",
            "option1": "Epidermis",
            "option2": "Dermis",
            "option3": "Subcutaneous tissue",
            "option4": "Superficial fascia",
            "option5": "Hair follicles",
            correctAnswer: 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which layer of the skin is involved in producing fingerprints?",
            "option1": "Epidermis",
            "option2": "Dermis",
            "option3": "Subcutaneous tissue",
            "option4": "Superficial fascia",
            "option5": "Stratum corneum",
            correctAnswer: 2
        }
    ] as Question[]
}
    // {
    //     "question": "What causes a sebaceous cyst?",
    //     "option1": "Obstruction of the sweat gland duct",
    //     "option2": "Obstruction of the sebaceous duct",
    //     "option3": "Infection of the nail fold",
    //     "option4": "Infection of the hair follicle",
    //     "option5": "Injury to the superficial fascia",
    //     correctAnswer: 2
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "What is the role of the hair papilla?",
    //     "option1": "Produce hair color",
    //     "option2": "Nourish the hair bulb",
    //     "option3": "Anchor the hair to the skin",
    //     "option4": "Produce sebum",
    //     "option5": "Innervate the hair follicle",
    //     correctAnswer: 2
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "Where are sweat glands NOT found?",
    //     "option1": "Palms",
    //     "option2": "Soles",
    //     "option3": "Red margins of the lips",
    //     "option4": "Forehead",
    //     "option5": "Armpits",
    //     correctAnswer: 3
    // },
    
    // {
    //     "question": "What is a paronychia?",
    //     "option1": "Infection of the hair follicle",
    //     "option2": "Infection of the sebaceous gland",
    //     "option3": "Infection between the nail and nail fold",
    //     "option4": "Staphylococcal infection of the superficial fascia",
    //     "option5": "Obstruction of the sebaceous duct",
    //     correctAnswer: 3
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "What is a boil commonly associated with?",
    //     "option1": "Infection of sweat glands",
    //     "option2": "Infection of the nail fold",
    //     "option3": "Infection of the hair follicle and sebaceous gland",
    //     "option4": "Obstruction of the sebaceous duct",
    //     "option5": "Fungal infection of the skin",
    //     correctAnswer: 3
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "What causes gooseflesh during a state of shock?",
    //     "option1": "Decreased blood flow",
    //     "option2": "Overactivity of the parasympathetic system",
    //     "option3": "Overactivity of the sympathetic system",
    //     "option4": "Infection",
    //     "option5": "Obstruction of sweat glands",
    //     correctAnswer: 3
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "How does a partial-skin-thickness burn heal?",
    //     "option1": "From the edges only",
    //     "option2": "From cells of the hair follicles, sebaceous glands, sweat glands, and edges",
    //     "option3": "From the superficial fascia",
    //     "option4": "Through natural regeneration of the dermis",
    //     "option5": "From the deep fascia",
    //     "ans": 2
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "What is required for the survival of a full-thickness skin graft?",
    //     "option1": "Superficial establishment of a new circulation",
    //     "option2": "Rapid establishment of a new circulation within it",
    //     "option3": "Removal of epidermal cells only",
    //     "option4": "Presence of subcutaneous tissue",
    //     "option5": "Connection to the original blood supply",
    //     "ans": 2
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "What is superficial fascia composed of?",
    //     "option1": "Dense connective tissue",
    //     "option2": "Adipose tissue only",
    //     "option3": "Loose areolar and adipose tissue",
    //     "option4": "Hyaline cartilage",
    //     "option5": "Fibrous bands",
    //     "ans": 3
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "What is a characteristic of split-thickness skin grafting?",
    //     "option1": "Includes the entire epidermis and dermis",
    //     "option2": "Removes only the superficial layer of the epidermis",
    //     "option3": "Leaves epidermal cells on the sides of the dermal papillae",
    //     "option4": "Does not require new blood supply establishment",
    //     "option5": "Used primarily for the scalp",
    //     "ans": 3
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "What happens to the skin over joints?",
    //     "option1": "It becomes thicker",
    //     "option2": "It always folds in the same place",
    //     "option3": "It loses all hair follicles",
    //     "option4": "It becomes highly pigmented",
    //     "option5": "It is devoid of sweat glands",
    //     "ans": 2
    // },
    // // {
        //     "question": "Where are sweat glands located?",
        //     "option1": "Epidermis",
        //     "option2": "Deep fascia",
        //     "option3": "Subcutaneous tissue",
        //     "option4": "Dermis",
        //     "option5": "Hair follicles",
        //     "ans": 4
        // },
        // {
    //     "question": "Where are hair follicles found?",
    //     "option1": "Only in the dermis",
    //     "option2": "In both the epidermis and dermis",
    //     "option3": "Only in the subcutaneous tissue",
    //     "option4": "In the deep fascia",
    //     "option5": "In the bones",
    //     "ans": 2
    // },
    // {
    //     "question": "What is the function of the arrector pili muscle?",
    //     "option1": "To anchor the hair to the skin",
    //     "option2": "To move the hair into a vertical position and cause gooseflesh",
    //     "option3": "To provide nutrients to the hair",
    //     "option4": "To produce sebum",
    //     "option5": "To innervate the hair follicle",
    //     "ans": 2
    // },
        
        // {
        //     "question": "What are Langer lines?",
        //     "option1": "Lines indicating stretch marks",
        //     "option2": "Lines formed by subcutaneous tissue",
        //     "option3": "Lines of cleavage in the dermis",
        //     "option4": "Lines of blood vessels",
        //     "option5": "Lines indicating skin tension",
        //     "ans": 3
        // },
        // {
        //     "question": "Which of the following is a type of sweat gland?",
        //     "option1": "Sebaceous gland",
        //     "option2": "Eccrine gland",
        //     "option3": "Ceruminous gland",
        //     "option4": "Mammary gland",
        //     "option5": "Endocrine gland",
        //     "ans": 2
        // },
        // {
        //     "question": "What is the role of the dermis in the skin?",
        //     "option1": "Nourishes the epidermis",
        //     "option2": "Produces sweat",
        //     "option3": "Synthesizes vitamin D",
        //     "option4": "Provides pigmentation",
        //     "option5": "Generates hair follicles",
        //     "ans": 1
        // },
        
    // {
    //     "question": "Which type of epithelium composes the epidermis?",
    //     "option1": "Simple squamous epithelium",
    //     "option2": "Stratified squamous epithelium",
    //     "option3": "Cuboidal epithelium",
    //     "option4": "Columnar epithelium",
    //     "option5": "Pseudostratified epithelium",
    //     "ans": 2
    // },
    // {
        //     "question": "What is the main function of arterioles within the dermis?",
        //     "option1": "Produce sebum",
        //     "option2": "Nourish the epidermis",
        //     "option3": "Regulate body temperature",
        //     "option4": "Generate sensory impulses",
        //     "option5": "Produce sweat",
        //     "ans": 3
        // },
        // {
        //     "question": "Which of the following statements about the epidermis is true?",
        //     "option1": "It is highly vascularized.",
        //     "option2": "It is composed mainly of collagen fibers.",
        //     "option3": "It contains melanocytes that produce melanin.",
        //     "option4": "It stores fat.",
        //     "option5": "It contains hair follicles.",
        //     "ans": 3
        // },
        // {
        //     "question": "What type of gland is responsible for producing earwax?",
        //     "option1": "Sebaceous gland",
        //     "option2": "Ceruminous gland",
        //     "option3": "Sweat gland",
        //     "option4": "Mammary gland",
        //     "option5": "Endocrine gland",
        //     "ans": 2
        // },
        // {
        //     "question": "Which of the following is NOT a layer of the epidermis?",
        //     "option1": "Stratum corneum",
        //     "option2": "Stratum lucidum",
        //     "option3": "Stratum granulosum",
        //     "option4": "Stratum basale",
        //     "option5": "Stratum dermis",
        //     "ans": 5
        // },
        // {
        //     "question": "Which of the following glands is NOT found in the skin?",
        //     "option1": "Sebaceous gland",
        //     "option2": "Ceruminous gland",
        //     "option3": "Sweat gland",
        //     "option4": "Mammary gland",
        //     "option5": "Thyroid gland",
        //     "ans": 5
        // },
        // {
        //     "question": "What type of fascia lies between the internal surfaces of musculoskeletal walls and serous membranes?",
        //     "option1": "Deep fascia",
        //     "option2": "Superficial fascia",
        //     "option3": "Subserous fascia",
        //     "option4": "Intermuscular septa",
        //     "option5": "Investing fascia",
        //     "ans": 3
        // },
        // {
        //     "question": "What is the primary role of the subcutaneous tissue?",
        //     "option1": "Heat regulation",
        //     "option2": "Providing skin pigmentation",
        //     "option3": "Sensory reception",
        //     "option4": "Vitamin D synthesis",
        //     "option5": "Fat storage",
        //     "ans": 5
        // },
        // {
        //     "question": "What type of burn damages only the epidermis?",
        //     "option1": "Partial-thickness burn",
        //     "option2": "Full-thickness burn",
        //     "option3": "4th-degree burn",
        //     "option4": "Superficial burn",
        //     "option5": "Deep partial-thickness burn",
        //     "ans": 4
        // },

        // ]}

